<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prahalad Belavadi&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.belavadi.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Prahalad Belavadi&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:18:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.belavadi.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ai and Copyright Law</title>
      <link>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/ai-and-copyright-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:18:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/ai-and-copyright-law/</guid>
      <description>How is copyright law handled today ?
Impact on Derivate works
Scope of public domain ?
Statute of Limitations on Patent or Copyright content
What quantifies as sufficient change to count as a work of original nature
Examples of prosecution using companies, self propreitorship and works of public domain
Different types of licenses
Who is prosecutable in terms of derived work of computer programs
What is considered Larceny
What is considered slander or libel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deriving Persona</title>
      <link>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/deriving-persona/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 20:02:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/deriving-persona/</guid>
      <description>Who do you want to be?
Persona is an unbiased equivalent of the word stereotype. Stereotypes imply people of this type, doing xy activities exhibit KM behaviour.
The idea of persona is interesting. You can literally be anyone you want. The type of activities you do, the type of discipline that is demanded of certain trades tend to leave an imprint. Heck, everything we do in life leaves an imprint on our psyche.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generic Advice</title>
      <link>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/generic-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 11:15:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/generic-advice/</guid>
      <description>I notice this trend where people are giving out advice. Not that there&amp;rsquo;s anything wrong with it. It&amp;rsquo;s just generic. The whole value proposition behind providing advice is to provide a perspective or a form of guidance perhaps on what needs to / can be done. The part about where this advice becomes valuable is when there is or has been skin in the game.
There are instances where people might recount incidences where others were a key subject and use that as reference for providing advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Learn</title>
      <link>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/how-i-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 02:42:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.belavadi.com/post/how-i-learn/</guid>
      <description>Process for Learning I suck at being consistent. I get distracted easily. Most learning content, I’ve either abandoned or skimmed. There’s very little I’ve actually finished, much less deeply in that scope.
For Structured Theory heavy Courses: I watch them while eating food. It’s intriguing.
Example: Behavioural Psychology by Robert Sapolsy on Youtube
For Structured Technical Content on Udemy or YouTube: Most Youtube content I end up rewatching if I catch something of interest or something of high technical detail that I have to have to implement to understand, I do a code-along with the instructor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
